<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kasam</string>
    <string name="option_background_content_description">Option Background</string>
    <string name="main_btn_text">Start</string>
    <string name="main_welcome">Welcome to KASAM Test</string>
    <string name="main_description">
        The concept of comprehension, the manageability and the meaningful aspect together form
        the prerequisites for the basic \"sense of context\"
        (KASAM) we carry with us on our journey through life. The sense of coherence is
        urgently an attitude that expresses the extent to which one has a lasting and
        pervasive sense of confidence in her/his ability to meet the different shifts of life.\n\n
        Please, mark your answer from 1 to 7 for the following 29 questions/statements to have your KASAM score.</string>
    <string name="main_edit_text_hint">Please, type your name!</string>
    <string name="problem">Problem occurred.</string>
    <string name="agree_terms_privacy">By continuing, you agree
        to the &lt;a href=https://sites.google.com/view/kasam-en-terms>Terms of Use&lt;/a> and
        the &lt;a href=https://sites.google.com/view/kasam-en-privacy-policy>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.</string>
    <string name="main_name_empty">Please, type your name to continue!</string>
    <string name="answers_missing">It seems you have gone through the questions
        but meanwhile, you missed one or some:\u0020</string>
    <string name="of">\u0020of\u0020</string>
    <string name="questions_show_result_btn">Click to view your results!</string>
    <string name="instruction">Click/Drag &amp; drop based on your best suit for each question/statement!</string>
    <string name="statements_title">\'s test</string>

    <string name="results_title">\'s results</string>
    <string name="result_header_m">Meaningful aspect</string>
    <string name="result_header_b">Concept of comprehension</string>
    <string name="result_header_h">Manageability</string>
    <string name="result_header_total">Total KASAM score</string>

    <string name="share_title">Sharing your results&#8230;</string>
    <string name="share_subject">Statistics from Kasam app</string>
    <string name="share_welcome">Here are results of %s\'s KASAM test.\n</string>
    <string name="share_main_scores">\nThe most important score and their values are the followings:\n
    Meaningful aspect: %s.\n
    Concept of comprehension: %s.\n
    Manageability: %s.\n
    Total KASAM score: %s.\n</string>
    <string name="share_results">\nHere are the outcomes of the result analysis:\n</string>
    <string name="share_details">\nHere are the details of the answer of each question:\n</string>
    <string name="share_note">\n* = Answers should be valued in reverse (7 should be 1, 1 should be 7, etc.).</string>

    <string name="share_from">\n\nShared from Kasam app</string>

    <string name="one">1</string>
    <string name="seven">7</string>

    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="eq">means:</string>
    <string name="about_label">About app</string>
    <string name="about_logo_content_description">About App Logo</string>
    <string name="about_mission_label">Mission</string>
    <string name="about_icons_label">Icons</string>
    <string name="about_documents_label">Documents</string>
    <string name="about_information_label">Information source</string>
    <string name="about_calculation_label">Result calculation</string>
    <string name="about_calculation1">Total KASAM score = M + B + H + Q3</string>
    <string name="about_calculation2">\nWhere M is the score of meaningful aspect, B is the score
    of concept of comprehension, H is the score of manageability and Q3 is the score of the 3rd question
    out of the all 29 ones.</string>

    <string name="about_mission1">
        There is no one who is happy, enthusiastic, contentious and at high levels of life in
        a very worrying, threatening and unpleasant life situation. There are people in every
        social class who are stuck in an unwanted situation, and who do not see a chance to
        break out. From time to time life is painful to all of us, when loved ones suffer and
        die when the one we love fools us or even children badly, etc. The one who has a
        strong KASAM is no more satisfied in such situations, but on the other hand, the
        KASAM strongly attempts to actively look at the context and influence the
        circumstances as well as possible, make the best of the situation, take care of what
        can make life bearable in the midst of its unpleasant. It is for this specific aspect
        of well-being that KASAM is important.
    </string>
    <string name="about_icons">The used icons are from the
        &lt;a href=https://material.io/tools/icons/?style=baseline>Material Design&lt;/a> web page.</string>
    <string name="about_documents1">
        By using the app, you hereby accept the
        &lt;a href=https://sites.google.com/view/kasam-en-terms>Terms of Use&lt;/a> and
        the &lt;a href=https://sites.google.com/view/kasam-en-privacy-policy>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.
    </string>
    <string name="about_documents2">This is a free software licensed under
        &lt;a href=https://www.gnu.org/licenses/agpl-3.0.en.html>GNU AGPL v3&lt;/a>.
    </string>
    <string name="about_information">For information about the KASAM test and more descriptions,
        please, click &lt;a href=https://www.skaraborg.se/globalassets/valfard/dokument/kasam-frageformular-----------------------29-fragor.pdf>
        here&lt;/a>.</string>
    <string name="about_mission2">\n
        The concept of comprehension is about the fact that both internal and
        external stimuli in life are thought to be structured, predictable and
        comprehensible.\n\n
Manageability refers to the degree to which it relies on its ability to make
        available the resources, both internal and external, necessary to meet
        all life events.\n\n
The meaningful aspect, ultimately, refers to the ability to see all situations,
        even demanding and problematic, as challenges worth investing time,
        dedication and energy in.
    </string>

    <string name="kasam_g_120_l_160_header">You are a healthy person</string>
    <string name="kasam_g_120_l_160_value">It appears that a reasonable overall average for healthy
        persons is around 140 KASAM total points. As your KASAM score is around 140, then it seems
    that you are a healthy person from the KASAM test perspective.</string>
    <string name="kasam_g_160_l_190_header">You are a strong KASAM person</string>
    <string name="kasam_g_160_l_190_value">As your KASAM score is greater than 160 but lower than 190,
        then it seems that you are a strong KASAM person. A true KASAM-strong person can face
        challenging challenges, and withstand more complexity in existence than a KASAM weak.</string>
    <string name="kasam_g_70_l_120_header">You are a weak KASAM person</string>
    <string name="kasam_g_70_l_120_value">As your KASAM score is greater than 70 but lower than 120,
        then it seems that you are a weak KASAM person. There is nothing wrong with being
        KASAM-weak, but you should think about lowering your ambition level, do not take too
        much responsibility and try to keep the level of difficulty in the challenges you assume.</string>

    <string name="kasam_l_120_l_100_header">You may be stuck in a situation</string>
    <string name="kasam_l_120_l_100_value">As you have less than 100 KASAM points,
        there is an obvious risk that you have stuck in your current situation, and it is
        recommended that you seek professional help (preferably a cognitive behavioral
        therapist), not to undergo psychotherapy, but for help to structure and initiate
        in a structured manner the implementation of a personal action plan.</string>
    <string name="kasam_l_120_low_m_header">You have low meaningful aspect value</string>
    <string name="kasam_l_120_low_m_value">As you have less than 30 points for meaningful aspect,
        it indicates lack
        of involvement in the everyday situations you are most often in. Then you should
        focus on developing your perspective ability,
        consider over the meaning of life and try to relinquish more from your own values
        ​​and do what you are good at, more often put into situations you like. It can also
        stand for depression and emotional fatigue. Sometimes it may be because you have
        linked your life to another person or group whose lifestyle / culture does not suit
        one\'s own.</string>
    <string name="kasam_l_120_low_b_header">You have low concept of comprehension value</string>
    <string name="kasam_l_120_low_b_value">As you have less than 35 points for concept of comprehension,
        it is apparent that the everyday life situation is more complex than at present
        having intellectual energy to cope, or having linguistic or social difficulties
        in its current environment. Sometimes weak B is caused by cognitive problems,
        the presence of too many negative and disturbing thoughts, the inability to
        self-control their reactions, poor self-esteem. Weak B sometimes has a clear
        connection to \"external control locus\".</string>
    <string name="kasam_l_120_low_h_header">You have low manageability value</string>
    <string name="kasam_l_120_low_h_value">As you have less than 35 points for manageability,
        it usually means lack of trust and resource weakness in relation to
        everyday requirements which can be caused by inadequate skills, poor economy,
        lack of togetherness, etc. It may also be because of the complexity of life when
        job, family, economics and others make greater demands than currently envisaged,
        and it has not yet been possible to develop enough functional new behaviors.
        A form of cognitive function that can be called self-esteem is also included in
        Manageability, that is, the ability to believe in being able to influence and be strong.</string>

    <string name="kasam_g_190_l_70_header">You are a suspicious person</string>
    <string name="kasam_g_190_l_70_value">More than 190 or less than 70 should cause suspicion of
        error-prompted instructions or lack of sincerity in the response. As you are in this
    category, please, make the test again.</string>
    <string name="result_arrow_content_description">Result Show Image</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>

    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>When you talk to people, do you feel that they do not understand you?</item>
        <item>Once you have had to do something that required collaboration with others, did you feel that it could be done?</item>
        <item>Think of the people you come into contact with daily, apart from those closest to you. How well do you know most of them?</item>
        <item>How often do you feel that you do not really care what is happening around you?</item>
        <item>Has it happened that you were surprised by the behavior of people you thought you felt well?</item>
        <item>Has it happened that people you trusted have disappointed you?</item>
        <item>Life is</item>
        <item>So far your life has</item>
        <item>How often do you feel unfairly treated?</item>
        <item>In the past ten years, your life has been</item>
        <item>Most things you do in the future are likely to be</item>
        <item>How often do you feel like you are in an unfamiliar situation and do not know what to do?</item>
        <item>How do you look at life?</item>
        <item>When you think about your life, it happens very often that you</item>
        <item>When you are facing a difficult problem, the solution is</item>
        <item>Your daily job is a source of</item>
        <item>In the future your life will probably be</item>
        <item>When something unpleasant happened before, you used to</item>
        <item>How often do you have much contradictory feelings and thoughts?</item>
        <item>When you do something that makes you feel comfortable</item>
        <item>How often does it happen that you have feelings within you that you prefer not to feel?</item>
        <item>You are determined that your personal life in the future will be</item>
        <item>Do you think there will always be people in the future that you can count on?</item>
        <item>How often does it happen that you have the feeling that you do not know exactly what is happening?</item>
        <item>Even a person with strong self-esteem can sometimes feel like an "unfortunate" one. How often do you feel that?</item>
        <item>When something has happened, you have usually found that</item>
        <item>When you think of difficulties that you are likely to face in important areas of your life, you have the feeling that</item>
        <item>How often do you feel there is no sense with the things you do in your daily life?</item>
        <item>How often do you have feelings you are not sure you can control?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answers_1">
        <item>I never have that feeling</item>
        <item>Certainly no</item>
        <item>I think they are strangers</item>
        <item>Very rarely or never</item>
        <item>It has never happened</item>
        <item>It has never happened</item>
        <item>More interesting with others</item>
        <item>Completely missed goals and meaning</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
        <item>Full of changes without knowing what comes next</item>
        <item>Totally fascinating</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
        <item>There is always a solution to the difficulties of life</item>
        <item>Feel how wonderful it is to live</item>
        <item>Always confusing and difficult to find</item>
        <item>Joy and deep satisfaction</item>
        <item>Full of changes without knowing what is happening next</item>
        <item>Love it over and over again</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
        <item>You will certainly continue to feel well at ease</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
        <item>Completely without purpose and meaning</item>
        <item>I am absolutely sure</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
        <item>Never</item>
        <item>You overrated or underestimated its significance</item>
        <item>You will always be able to overcome the difficulties</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answers_7">
        <item>I always have that feeling</item>
        <item>Certainly yes</item>
        <item>I know them very well</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
        <item>It has often happened</item>
        <item>It has often happened</item>
        <item>Better completely alone</item>
        <item>Been full of goals and meaning</item>
        <item>Very rarely / never</item>
        <item>Completely predictable without surprising changes</item>
        <item>Completely boring</item>
        <item>Very rarely / never</item>
        <item>There is no solution to the difficulties of life</item>
        <item>Ask yourself why, at all, it exists</item>
        <item>Completely sunny</item>
        <item>Pain and suffering</item>
        <item>Completely predictable and without surprising changes</item>
        <item>Say \"get it\" and then move on</item>
        <item>Very rarely / never</item>
        <item>Something will certainly happen that disturbs your good feeling</item>
        <item>Very rarely / never</item>
        <item>Filled with goals and meaning</item>
        <item>I doubt that</item>
        <item>Very rarely / never</item>
        <item>Very often</item>
        <item>You saw the matter in its correct proportion</item>
        <item>You will not be able to overcome the difficulties</item>
        <item>Very rarely / never</item>
        <item>Very rarely / never</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
